{
    "subject": "resource/Don_Gummer",
    "predicate": "ontology/training",
    "object": "resource/Herron_School_of_Art_and_Design",
    "human_readable": "Don Gummer received training at Herron School of Art and Design.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9756503105163574,
            "question": "Could Don Gummer have learned sculpture at Herron School of Art and Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8483184576034546,
            "question": "Where did Don Gummer receive his training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7910601496696472,
            "question": "What kind of school is Herron School of Art and Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7219682335853577,
            "question": "Are there other famous artists who attended Herron School of Art and Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6941015720367432,
            "question": "Is Don Gummer an artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6735468506813049,
            "question": "What are some examples of art forms taught at Herron School of Art and Design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6497554779052734,
            "question": "Does Don Gummer's training influence his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5626025795936584,
            "question": "How does attending a specialized school like Herron School of Art and Design benefit an artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38694262504577637,
            "question": "What might Don Gummer's work focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14523755013942719,
            "question": "What is the importance of art education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Don Gummer received training at Herron School of Art and Design.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might Don Gummer's work focus on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does attending a specialized school like Herron School of Art and Design benefit an artist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Don Gummer's training influence his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8364_51.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the documents does not support the triple \"Don Gummer received training at Herron School of Art and Design.\" While Don Gummer's name is mentioned in the context information, there is no indication that he received training at Herron School of Art and Design. In fact, his name appears in a list of notable alumni, but it does not specify what program or degree he completed."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Don Gummer is a notable alumnus of the Herron School of Art and Design, which implies he received training there."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Don Gummer is a film producer and the ex-husband of Meryl Streep, and according to his biography, he attended the California Institute of the Arts (CalArts), not Herron School of Art and Design.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}